{
  "formulas":
    {
      "Abb_multipl_formulas": [
        {
          "question": "Разность кубов:",
          "formula": "\\(x^3-y^3= ?\\) ",
          "answer1": "$$(x-y)(x^2+xy+y^2)$$",
          "answer2": "$$(x-y)(x^2-2xy-y^2)$$",
          "answer3": "$$(x-y)(x^2-xy-y^2)$$",
          "answer4": "$$(x+y)(x^2-2xy+y^2)$$",
          "correct": "$$(x-y)(x^2+xy+y^2)$$"
        },
        {
          "question": "Сумма кубов:",
          "formula": "\\(x^3+y^3= ?\\) ",
          "answer1": "$$(x+y)(x^2-xy+y^2)$$",
          "answer2": "$$(x+y)(x^2+2xy+y^2)$$",
          "answer3": "$$(x+y)(x^2+xy+y^2)$$",
          "answer4": "$$(x+y)(x^2-2xy+y^2)$$",
          "correct": "$$(x+y)(x^2-xy+y^2)$$"
        },
        {
          "question": "Квадрат суммы:",
          "formula": "\\((x+y)^2= ?\\) ",
          "answer1": "$$x^2+xy+y^2$$",
          "answer2": "$$x^2+y^2$$",
          "answer3": "$$x^2-2xy+y^2$$",
          "answer4": "$$x^2+2xy+y^2$$",
          "correct": "$$x^2+2xy+y^2$$"
        },
        {
          "question": "Квадрат разности:",
          "formula": "\\((x-y)^2= ?\\) ",
          "answer1": "$$x^2-2xy+y^2$$",
          "answer2": "$$x^2-y^2$$",
          "answer3": "$$x^2-2xy-y^2$$",
          "answer4": "$$x^2-xy+y^2$$",
          "correct": "$$x^2-2xy+y^2$$"
        },
        {
          "question": "Разность квадратов:",
          "formula": "\\(x^2-y^2= ?\\) ",
          "answer1": "$$x^2-xy+y^2$$",
          "answer2": "$$x^2-2xy-y^2$$",
          "answer3": "$$(x+y)(x-y)$$",
          "answer4": "$$(x-y)^2$$",
          "correct": "$$(x+y)(x-y)$$"
        },
        {
          "question": "Куб суммы:",
          "formula": "\\((x+y)^3= ?\\) ",
          "answer1": "$$x^3+3x^2y+3xy^2+y^3$$",
          "answer2": "$$x^3-3x^2y+3xy^2-y^3$$",
          "answer3": "$$x^3+y^3$$",
          "answer4": "$$x^3+3xy+y^3$$",
          "correct": "$$x^3+3x^2y+3xy^2+y^3$$"
        },
        {
          "question": "Куб разности:",
          "formula": "\\(x^3-y^3= ?\\) ",
          "answer1": "$$x^3-3x^2y+3xy^2-y^3$$",
          "answer2": "$$x^3-3xy-y^3$$",
          "answer3": "$$x^3-3x^2y+3xy^2-y^3$$",
          "answer4": "$$x^3+3x^2y+3xy^2-y^3$$",
          "correct": "$$x^3-3x^2y+3xy^2-y^3$$"
        }
      ],
      "Geometry_figures": [
        {
          "question": "Easy Questions Answer A",
          "formula": "Easy Questions Answer A",
          "answer1": "A) A",
          "answer2": "B) B",
          "answer3": "C) C",
          "answer4": "D) D",
          "correct": "A) A"
        },
        {
          "question": "Easy Questions Answer B",
          "formula": "Easy Questions Answer A",
          "answer1": "A) A",
          "answer2": "B) B",
          "answer3": "C) C",
          "answer4": "D) D",
          "correct": "B) B"
        }
      ],
      "Rad_to_Degrees": [
        {
          "question": "Easy Questions Answer A",
          "formula": "Easy Questions Answer A",
          "answer1": "A) A",
          "answer2": "B) B",
          "answer3": "C) C",
          "answer4": "D) D",
          "correct": "A) A"
        }
      ],
      "StereometriaSquares": [
        {
          "question": "Easy Questions Answer A",
          "formula": "Easy Questions Answer A",
          "answer1": "A) A",
          "answer2": "B) B",
          "answer3": "C) C",
          "answer4": "D) D",
          "correct": "A) A"
        }
      ]
    }
}